God is still saying something.
On Sunday the 20th of April 2014 during a live Sunday Service at The SCOAN,
Prophet T.B. Joshua gave a prophetic message concerning an attack
which he saw would occur in a French-speaking country.
These were his words.
In a French country, this is France,
I'm seeing an attack;
there will be an attack there.
They should take note of Wednesday and Thursday.
I will ask them to play it on Emmanuel TV.
The following week, during The SCOAN live service on Sunday the 27th of April 2014,
Prophet T.B. Joshua spoke further about the vision God had given him
concerning the French-speaking country.
He mentioned that the perpetrators were still in town
and specified the location in which he saw the attack occur - Paris, the capital city of France.
These were his words.
The nation, a French-speaking country which I said last Sunday -
these people are still in the town - French-speaking.
I was saying last week in Paris - that was the location I saw last week.
Breaking News, out of Paris, an attack at the office of a well-known French satirical magazine
has left at least 10 people dead.
We are hearing two heavily armed gun men stormed into Charlie Hebdo's office in Paris.
You may recall that office was fire bombed and severely damaged several years ago
in response to cartoons about the Prophet Mohammed.
We will go straight to CNN's Jim Bitterman in Paris.
Jim, bring us the very latest update. 10 dead, among them police officers.
That's according to the prosecutor's office; it could actually be higher than that.
We are still waiting for confirmation.
There are numbers that are being reported as high as 11
that have been killed in this attack this morning and the number of people injured.
Basically, the gun men, according to eye witnesses, went into the offices
during the editorial meeting this morning
as editors, reporters and cartoonists had gathered around and started shooting.
The attack went on for about five minutes and according to some eye witnesses,
the attackers were armed with a rocket launcher as well as some machine guns.
It looks like it was a very well prepared attack.
The men were dressed in black. The two men were dressed in black.
Police gave pursuit, and a number of police officers have been injured,
one, as you mentioned, may have been killed,
pursing the gun men as they were running away from the scene.
In a French country, this is France.
I'm seeing an attack;
there will be an attack there.
They should take note of Wednesday and Thursday.
I will ask them to play it on Emmanuel TV.
We believe that you have been inspired by the clip that you have just watched.
Click here to subscribe to witness more of God's power at work in our generation today
and stay up-to-date with the latest prophecies, deliverances,
sermons and testimonies from The SCOAN.
Emanuel TV - Changing lives, Changing nations, and Changing the world.
RV: Mel Flowers 06/04/2019